Finding Aid for the Grantland Rice Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Correspondence - Incoming
  - Correspondence, incoming -- letters from All-American football players
    The following letters were sent to Grantland Rice c/o Ralph Edwards' "This Is Your Life" radio program when he was featured on the program in December 1948. The letters are from members of Grantland Rice's All-America football teams over a period of years. They have been removed the brown leather scrap-book initialed HGR (in which they were presented to him) and interfiled alphabetically with the rest of the incoming correspondence. Name of writer and date of letter are given below.
    - Frank Albert, 28 Dec 1948 (Box 2)
    - Ki Aldrich, 9 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Buss B. Baldwin, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Angelo Bertelli, 4 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Ernest E. Blandin, 10 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Arthur Boeringer, 1 Feb 1949 (Box 2)
    - Vic Bottari, 10 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Joe M. Boyd, 13 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Paul Christman, 3 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Paul H. Gleary, 22 Dec 1948 (Box 2)
    - Averell E. Daniel, 4 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Carl H. Diehl, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Bobby Dodd, 25 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Joseph C. Donchess, 3 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Dick Duden, 20 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Lawrence S. Sly, 14 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Beattie Feathers, 13 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Bob Fenimore, 11 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - John Ferraro, 23 Lee 1949 (Box 2)
    - Wesley E. Fesler, 13 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Patrick J. Fildey, 7 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Ed Franco, 26 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Harry Gilmer, 7 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Willis A. Glassgow, 3 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Marshall Goldberg, 15 Feb 1949 (Box 2)
    - Paul Governali, 4 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Robert H. Grayson, 7 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Tom Harmon, 19 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Carl C. Hinkle, Jr., 27 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Jimmy Hitchcock, 11 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Bud Holland, n.d. (Box 2)
    - Linde11 Houston, 8 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Weldon G. Humble, 26 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - William Hutson, 7 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Morton Kaer, 27 Lee 1948 (Box 2)
    - Mai Kutner, 18 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Johnny Lujack, 5 Feb 1949 (Box 2)
    - Francis L. Lund, 17 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Vaughn Mancha, 17 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - John Mastrangelo, 7 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - J. Banks McFadden, 4 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Ed McMillan, 24 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Creighton E. Miller, 13 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Don C. Miller, 25 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Anthony A. Minisi, 7 Feb 1949 (Box 2)
    - Leroy Monsky, 12 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Bronko Nagenski, 19 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Torn Nash, 17 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Ernie Nevers, 6 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - David O'Brien, 19 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Duane Purvis, 10 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Jesse Quatse, 3 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Bob Reinhard, 28 Dec 1948 (Box 2)
    - Ernest J. Rentner, 6 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Hugh M. Rhea, 2 Feb 1949 (Box 2)
    - Esco Sarkkinen, 19 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - George H. Sauer, 3 Feb 1949 (Box 2)
    - Paul T. Scull, 24 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Bill Seviachy(?), 4 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Gaius Shaver, 21 Dec 1948 (Box 2)
    - Bernie A. Shively, 14 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Fred Sington, 3 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Joseph P. Skladany, 13 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Bruce Smith, 7 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Ernie F. Smith, 28 Dec 1948 (Box 2)
    - John H. Smith, 13 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - John P. Smith, 6 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Orland F. Smith, 3 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Joseph B. Steffy, Jr., 3 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Ken Strong, 17 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Harry Stuhldreher, n.d. (Box 2)
    - R.L. Suffridge, 11 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Steven Sukey, 18 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Milton F. Summerfelt, 17 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Irvine Warburton, 28 Dec 1948 (Box 2)
    - Gilbert L. Welch, 5 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Jac Weiler, 27 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Don Whitmire, 18 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Frank H. Wickhorst, 10 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Robert Wilson, 24 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - Bowden Wyatt, 14 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
    - unsigned, 8 Jan 1949 (Box 2)
- World war I papers - orders, passes etc. (Box 2)
- Manuscript writings of Grantland Rice (Box 3)
  - Verse (Box 3, Folder 1-20)
    - Add Verse (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Advanced Wisdom (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Alumnus Football (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - An American Soldier Speaks (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - The Ancient Call (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - The Answer (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Armistice Day 1931 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Armistice Day 1941 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Army and Navy (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "Army and Navy--the Blue and the Gray--" (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - As for Resolutions in General (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "As this old world goes roun' and roun'.. ." (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - As We Grow Older (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - At the Year's Dawn (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "As long as there's a job to do" (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Back Home Again (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "Back to your sheltering shadows we must turn" (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Base Camp No. 1 Speaks (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - The Battle Line (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "Before my early songs were sung" (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "The bells of the city are ringing" (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Beyond All Things (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Beyond Us (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - The Big Chance (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "Bill Jones had been the shining star" (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Breaker and Maker (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "Brain--you are gone--" (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - "Breath of roses--the south wind blowing" (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Brest -- St. Nazaire ... (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "By sun and snow, by palm and pine" (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - "By wind and wave, by palm and pine" (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - California Speaks (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "Columbus found a gentle land" (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - The Commodore Flag (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - The Competitor Speaks (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Concerning Veterans (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - A Confession (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "The cove who never kids himself" (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - "Czar, Chiota and Gay one day" (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - "The day is cold and dreary ..." (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Deep South (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "Down where the southwind's calling" (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Dregs and Apple Blossoms (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "Dreamer of dreams that come true" (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - The Drift Eternal (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - The Duffer's Estate (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 'Failed to Return' (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "Fate called a quitter from the crowd" (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "Father, Who gave but taketh back from me" (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - A Few Lines to Ernie Pyle (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - A Few Memories 1918-1934 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - The Final Fort (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - A First-Tee Forecast (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Flag of Our Country (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - "Flag of our country, flying forever" (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Flag of Our Fathers (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - For the New Year (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - "For the thunder is back upon us" (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - The Forty-Eight Report, or The U.S. Goes to War (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - "A friend or two and a dream or two" (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - From Down Under (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "From Golden Gate through cotton fields" (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - The Game and the Piper (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Game Called (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "Game called by darkness--" (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "Gather your touchdowns while you may" (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - The Gift of the Gods (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "Give us our dreams, they call" (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - "Good bye, dear heart" (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Good Luck and Bad (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "Good luck is like a down hill tide" (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Good Night that Means Good Bye (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "(Gray) shadows gather and the wind is crying" (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - "He lets a few go longer than he lets the others go" (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - "'He played the game'--" (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "He saw long lines of khaki form" (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Her Prayer (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - "Here comes the wanderer over the plain" (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "Here I shall wait" (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "Here is my traveler's cloak, dusty and torn" (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - "Here is the test when from down under" (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "Here is your pick--from palm to fir" (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - "Here was the flame that flared beyond the night" (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - "How low the candle burns" (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - "A 100 years of sweetness" (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Hymn of Hate (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - "I called them from their ancient homes" (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "I give you Romance--in each crowded street" (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - "I have learned something well worth while" (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "I knew a kid one day" (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - "I saw him sprawled and broken in the mud" (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - I Still Remember (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - "I waited for the dawn to break" (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "I wandered among the graves today" (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - "I, who have lived in crowds" (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - I wish I Was the Fellow (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - "I wonder, when you hear the north wind blowing" (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "If I may call you friend" (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "If I should ever get too old to dream" (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "If it should be we will not come" (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - "I'm going home some day --" (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - "I'm home again where the saddle's calling" (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - The Indestructible Rick (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - "Into what mist and fog ahead" (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - "Into your lidless eyes I stand and stare" (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - "It may be that in some far sky" (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "It may be that tomorrow I will turn" (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - "It's a hell of a course, the golfer cried" (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - "I've piked along it for some fifty years" (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - "Just at the first tee,,with a sigh" (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - A Knife in the Heart (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - "Land of old dreams ..." (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - The Last Port" (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Let's Wake Up (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Lexington, April 19, 1775 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - "Life, and the ease I knew" (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Lines on Again Looking into Keats' Lines 'On First Looking into Chapman's Homer' (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Lines on the Occasion of the National Amateur Golf Championship (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Lines to a Howitzer (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Lines to Fate (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - "Little girl, little girl" (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - The Long iioad (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - The Main Ingredient (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - A Message from the Front Line (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - The Missing Ingredient (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - More April Madness (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - More Philosophy (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - "My name is Trouble--I'm a busy bloke--" (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - My Native Land (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - "My voice is not Caruso's" (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - The New King Cobra at the Bronx Park Zoo (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - The New Romance (Box 3)
    - "Night comes--and the night comes on apace" (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - "No one ever told me what it meant to be.. ." (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - "No HVelcome Home' could mean as much" (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Nocturne (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - "Nothin' to say 'gainst the Northland" (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - "Now all the golden harmonies are still" (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - The Old Cumberland's Callin', Come Home (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - The Old Doc with the Scythe (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - "Old Montana, Arizona, California, Maine" (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - The Old-Timer (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - One Way Out (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Only the Brave (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Only the Unafraid (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Over the Score (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Past Glories 13 Peace--and the A.E.F. 13 A Philosophy 13 Prelude to Passing (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - The Heturning Vagabond (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "2iver that's flowing ..." (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Road's End 13 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - "The roaring guns are bigger now" (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - The Rookie and the Vet (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - The Rougher Road (Box 3)
    - The Shadow of the Fir 14 "The sheep's in the meadow" (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "Side by side on the bench" (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - "Sing, birds from silver tree tops" (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Singing to You (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - The Six Inch Speaks (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Some Day (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - "Some one, I thought, is singing-some loved slong" (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Somewhere Back (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - A Soldier's Faith (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "The song dies out--only the dream remains" (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Song of the Trail (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Song of the Unafraid (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Song of the Unwhipped (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Song of the Winds (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Songs above Dust (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Spring's Reveille (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - "The sun is fading in the west" (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - "Take, if you will, my house and lot" (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - "Take your fame as you find it" (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Taking Your Pick (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Thanks for-- (Box 3)
    - "There are all the millions who are chained to desk or den" (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - "There are fighters who are giants" (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - "There are ghosts that wave and beckon" (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "There are two places" (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "There is an end to every path" (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "There is a test when from down under" (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "There must be fields beyond us" (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "There was a time I liked the brilliant glow" (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - "There was another spring" (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - "There's a long dull hike" (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - "There's a road's end, mates, for every trip" (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "These are my native hills that call me home" (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - "They do not know the starry heights of fame" (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - "They know deep in their dreams" (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "They say that Ruth, at 38" (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "This is the way I figure life" (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - "This is the way things work" (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "This (is) your game, old pal" (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "This is to make you more than merry" (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - The Three Musketeers (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - "Through all life's weariness" (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Through the Fog (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - "Tilt up your long, black, ugly snout" (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - "The time has long since drifted by" (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - To Billy Phelps, The Golden Boy of Yale (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - "To bother not too greatly" (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - To Judy Howard on Her Birthday (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - To Kit (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - To Mother Hollis on Her 100th Birthday (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - To Poetry (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - To Sport and Spring (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - To the Last of All (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - To Understand (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - The Trainers (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - "The turmoil and the strife is done" (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 23 Years Later (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Two Places (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "Under this banner of Seven Stars" (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - The Unwhipped (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - "Upon our shield the staining rust" (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - The U.S. at War (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - The U.S. Goes to War (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Voices from the Dust (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - "Waiting now for the training trip" (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - The Wanderers (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - "Wars may be on again" (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "We are only the Dead today" (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - "We are the ones to watch someday" (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - We Have with Us Today after the Battle (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - "We heard afar the Clarion Call" (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - "We know how brief the sail is" (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - "We, who are broken and battered" (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - "We who have known the rougher road" (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - "We've got a war to win" (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - "What am I fighting for?" (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "What are you a.fter, speed?" (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "What is there left to say?" (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - "What waits beyond this war" (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "When I am dust" (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - "When I am old and April days" (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - "When I am old, as years are measured" (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - "'When I was one andtwenty" (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "When rain-wet crosses know the dawn that gleams" (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Where the Sambier Rose is Calling (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - "Whether it's Heaven,--or whether it's Hell" (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - "Who are the brave? I've asked this deep in doubt" (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - "Who shall say when the game is done" (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "Wind harps from the south again" (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - The Winner (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Winter's End (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - "Write this one passage in your Book of Strife" (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - "You can sleep gentler now" (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - "You mark them out in street or club" (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - "You mean a summer's day, when skies are blue" (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - "You thought that the south wind was sighing" (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Articles (Box 3, Folder 21-31)
    Articles include the following: "Rex Beach" (17 typed pages, with corrections in pencil and ink), "New All-Timer" (on Bill Dickey)(7 typed pages, with corrections in pencil), "Pound for Pound" (on Harry Greb)(7 typed pages), "The Only Jones, or Just One Bobby" (20 typed pages, with corrections in pencil), Babe Ruth elegy (4-page typed carbon), "Sportlight" on ideal baseball team ( 2 typed pages with corrections in pencil), "Sportlight" on horse racing (2-page typed fragment), "Ex-Champions" (l-page typed fragment), Gene Tunney (7 typed pages with corrections in pencil), "The 'Umblin' Game" (on golf)(13 typed pages with corrections in pencil), "The Season As I See It" (on baseball, 1947) (5 page typed carbon with additions in pencil).
  - Radio Scripts, Radio scripts include interviews with Dr. Andrews (on fossils)(2-page typed fragment), Ford Bond (4 typed pages with corrections in pencil), Irvin S. Cobb (l page, typed and holograph), T.A.D. Jones (4 typed pages), Gustavus Kirby (3-page typed carbon), Ring Lardner (2 versions: 3 typed pages with corrections in pencil, 2-page fair copy, typed), Lou Little (with Ford Bond)(2 typed pages), Eddie Rickenbacker (3 typed pages), Ralph Sasse (3-page typed carbon), Al ---- (baseball statistician) (3 typed pages with corrections in pencil). (Box 3, Folder 32-35)
  - Play Fragments, Untitled play, fragmentary (13 typed pages), has the following characters: (Act I) Rip Jones, Jenny Jones, Brink Thorn, Langdon Brown, (Act II) Marie, Babyface, Foley. (Box 3, Folder 36-37)
  - Miscellaneous, Miscellaneous manuscripts include: a short story, "The Other Man-and the Other Woman" (4 typed pages); football preview (2-page typed carbon); notes on post-college careers of football All-Americans (1 typed page + carbon); "Sports Parade 1933" (4-page typed list); 2-page typed list of athletes, untitled; Look's 1949 Ail-American Football Team (1-page list, typed carbon, signed by Grantland Rice, Hal Middlesworth, and Tim Gohane); 2 Sport Parade captions, "Running out an Ancient Grudge," and "The Driving Iron That Won Four Crowns" (each 1 typed page with corrections in pencil); "The Third Olympic Winter Games" (11 typed pages, numbered 12); "Questions and suggestions for All American selections" (2-page typed carbon); "Sports Parade 1934-1935" (8-page typed list)5 card index to manuscript verse (43 typed 3 x 5 cards, with titles, first lines etc). (Box 3, Folder 38-44)
- Newspaper clippings of poems, articles, and columns by Grantland Rice
  - Index of all poems, articles, and columns by Grantland Rice
    Includes a few poems published in places other than GR's daily columns. Index is to titles only (except in the case of untitled poems, which are entered by first line or portion thereof); when a title is followed by more than one citation in the index, this may indicate either different poems with the same title or more than one occurrence of the same poem. First number given in each case indicates box, second indicates folder.
    - Aaron to Moses (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Abdul's Viewpoint (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - About March, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - About Michigan and Ohio State (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - About Nashville's Best Paper (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - About Spring Training (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Above the Darkness (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Above the Drumfire (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - The Absent Ingredient (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Absolved (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Across the Ways (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Adam's Advantage (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - The Advance (Box 5, Folder 1, Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Advance Apology (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - The Advance Call (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Advance Echoes (Box 5, Folder 27, Box 6, Folder 8, Box 7, Folder 11)
    - The Advance Guard (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Advance Nod to Spring (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Advance Wraiths (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Advice to a Baffled World (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Africa, Poor Africa (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - After a Vacation (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - After a Workout (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - After All (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - "After Blenheim" in Georgia (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - "After Blenheim"--or July First (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - After Interviewing the Tourists (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - After the Charge 5-27 (Box 6, Folder 3, Box 7, Folder 36)
    - After the Coin (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - After the Game (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - After the Message, "Killed in Action (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - After the Past Three Days --and Nights (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - After Thinking It Over (Box 5, Folder 7, Box 7, Folder 21)
    - After Working Hours (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - The Aftermath (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - The Aftermath of "The Beautiful" (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Afterwards (Box 5, Folder 6, Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Against the Game's Break (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Against Time (Box 5, Folder 4, Box 6, Folder 44)
    - "Ah, distinctly I remember" (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Air King (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Alan Seeger (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Alexander the Great (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Alias--"The Blue and the Gray" (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - The Alibi Eternal (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Alibi-ing the Boost (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Alice in Blunderland (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - The Alien (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - The All-American Parade (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - All Ready for Its Annual Cruise (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - The All-Star Parade No.6 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - All-Time All-America (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - The All-Time Fullback (Box 6, Folder 5, 6)
    - Almost by O. Goldsmith (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Along the Way (Box 4, Folder 19, 29)
    - Already There (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Also Others (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Alumnus Football 4-23 (Box 6, Folder 60, Box 7, Folder 9)
    - America's "Big Four" (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - America's National Game (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Ancestral Quarries (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - The Ancient Lure (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - The Ancient Squeal (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - And Far Away (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "And its Ho for the land" (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - And So It Goes (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - And So. 'What of It? (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - And Then He Took Up Golf (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - And Yet-- 4-1 (Box 5, Folder 21, Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Anent Young Corbett's Recent Spiel (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Annual Bugler (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - The Annual Chorus (Box 5, Folder 3, Box 6, Folder 29)